nofilmschool.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://nofilmschool.com and NONETWORK, LLC and governs data collection and usage.

## Collection of your Personal Information

NONETWORK may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NONETWORK. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NONETWORK website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through NONETWORK's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

NONETWORK encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NONETWORK so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. NONETWORK is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NONETWORK website.

## Use of your Personal Information

NONETWORK collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

NONETWORK may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NONETWORK and its affiliates. NONETWORK may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

NONETWORK does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

NONETWORK may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. NONETWORK may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email, or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NONETWORK, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

NONETWORK may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NONETWORK, in order to determine what NONETWORK services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NONETWORK to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

NONETWORK will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NONETWORK or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NONETWORK; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NONETWORK, or the public.

## Use of Cookies

The NONETWORK website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NONETWORK pages, or register with NONETWORK site or services, a cookie helps NONETWORK to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NONETWORK website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NONETWORK features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NONETWORK services or websites you visit.

## Interest-based ads

When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and elsewhere on the Internet about products and services you might like. This website does not collect the information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To find out more about interest-based advertising or to opt out, [click this link](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising.

## Security of your Personal Information

NONETWORK secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NONETWORK by selecting the "Unsubscribe" link included in all NONETWORK communications.

## Changes to Policy

NONETWORK reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Privacy Policy under which http://nofilmschool.com is offered. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will supersede all previous versions. NONETWORK encourages you to periodically review the Policy to stay informed of our updates.

## Contact Us

NONETWORK welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Privacy Policy:

NONETWORK, LLC

PO Box 4668 #39920

New York, NY 10163-4668

Email Address: contact@nofilmschool.com

_Last updated September 24, 2014_
